<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LR_Cook</string>
    <string name="name">Cooking recipes</string>
    <string name="eat1">Breakfast</string>
    <string name="eat2">Lunch</string>
    <string name="eat3">Dinner</string>
    <string name="change_lang">Change language</string>
    <string name="fio">Kazunina Sofya T-403901 ISIT</string>
    <string name="lang_en">English</string>
    <string name="lang_ru">Russian</string>
    <string name="lang_fr">French</string>
    <string name="breakfest1_name">FRIED EGGS IN A FRYING PAN</string>
    <string name="breakfest2_name">CROUTONS FROM A LOAF WITH AN EGG</string>
    <string name="breakfest3_name">SEMOLINA PORRIDGE WITH MILK</string>
    <string name="breakfest3_ingrid">Milk-300 ml Semolina-3 tables.l. Sugar-1 tablespoon. Salt-to taste Butter-40g</string>
    <string name="breakfest2_ingrid">White bread-300g Eggs-1 pc. Milk-50ml Butter-40g Salt-to taste</string>
    <string name="breakfest1_ingrid">Eggs-1 pc. Butter-10g Salt-to taste Ground hot pepper-to taste</string>
    <string name="btn_next">Next</string>
    <string name="ingridients">Ingredients</string>
    <string name="cooking">Cooking</string>
    <string name="breakfest1_cooking">1. Prepare the necessary ingredients. Wash the egg with soap under a stream of warm water. This is necessary to ensure safety and protection from possible salmonella infection.\n\n    2. Heat a frying pan with low sides over high heat. Add a piece of butter and melt it to a liquid state. Reduce the heat to medium.\n\n    3. Beat the egg into a frying pan with hot oil. Try not to damage the integrity of the yolk. Distribute the protein in a circular motion so that it spreads evenly over the pan.\n\n    4. Fry the scrambled eggs until the protein is completely set, and the yolk is still bright yellow and liquid.\n\n    5. After the scrambled eggs have reached the required degree of readiness, you can lightly add salt and pepper to taste.</string>
    <string name="breakfest1_time">15 min</string>
    <string name="breakfest2_time">15 min</string>
    <string name="breakfest3_time">10 min</string>
    <string name="breakfest2_cooking">1. Prepare the products according to the list. Prepare a deep wide bowl and a frying pan. 2. In a deep bowl, beat the egg lightly, add salt or sugar if you are making sweet croutons. Pour in the milk and mix everything together.3 . Dip each slice of bread into the mixture so that it is well soaked. 4. Put the pan on medium heat, put the butter on it and wait until it melts completely.\\n     5. Place slices of bread in the egg mixture on a frying pan heated with oil and fry until a yellow-golden crust forms, first on one side, then, carefully turning over, on the other side. 6. Serve ready-made croutons from a loaf with egg and milk immediately. This is an independent dish.</string>
    <string name="breakfest3_cooking">1. To prepare semolina porridge, prepare all the ingredients. Milk for porridge can be used of any fat content. 2. It is convenient to use aluminum dishes or a saucepan with a thick bottom for cooking porridge. Pour the required amount of milk into the ladle. 3. Add a spoonful of sugar and a pinch of salt to the milk. 4. Then add semolina to the cold milk. Stir and put the ladle on the fire. If you like porridge more liquid, then only 2 tablespoons of cereals will be enough. 5. With constant stirring, bring everything to a boil. When boiling, the porridge will gradually become thick. Boil it, literally, for 20-30 seconds and remove from heat. Just do not stop stirring the porridge, otherwise you will get one big lump. It is not difficult to stand and wait for 1-2 minutes to boil. 6. Pour the finished porridge into a prepared plate, add a small amount of butter or fresh berries.</string>
</resources>